<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>A Washed-up Nerd</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on A Washed-up Nerd</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Credits</title><link>/showcase/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/showcase/</guid><description>The team admires these presenters and organizations, who hosted the invaluable IELTS learning video series, lessons, and resources on the web to students as free content.
Content Owners Presenter Website Margot Politis (ABC) Study English: IELTS Preparation The team would also like to thank the other fellow content aggregators, who aggregated great IELTS resources. They made our work more presentable to readers.</description></item><item><title>A Beginner's Guide to IELTS</title><link>/post/hello/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/post/hello/</guid><description>Hi Readers,
I planned to move as a resident to Canada when I got the feeling that being in the US was limiting the uprising of dreamy ideas. The brief unemployment consumed the expiring student work permit like a symbiote, it then shapeshifted as the visa issues.
I was also fascinated to design an artificially intelligent travel platform. So, I had to take the IELTS test in Boston, MA. In the following posts, you will understand my choices of words, the writing style, and the cohesion as an author.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>When did we start When I took the IELTS in April 2018, I curated the collection of IELTS preparation video series, resources (materials and notes) and practice activities.
Who can use and how can it be used We post reviews of various resources for Reading, Listening, Writing and Speaking sections in IELTS. All the content is readily available and without signing up for any subscriptions.
We recommend the readers to only use the reviewed notes and video series for preparing to IELTS test and not redistribute it.</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/archive/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Prajwal</title><link>/authors/prajwal/prajwal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/prajwal/prajwal/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>